Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Go upstairs. Find my mother.
Take her to the gatehouse.
Do not leave her side.
Here. Dry yourself off.
You've had quite a shock.
Sorry.
- It's for my own protection.
- Your protection?
Exhuming your sister's body.
- Hardly rational. is it?
- No. no. no. no. no.
Don't… Don't try to make it out
- like I'm the dangerous one.
- I always feared this day would come.
- That I would find out?
- That you would show signs
of your mother's affliction.
Is my sister still alive?
- Oh. Sherlock. For God's sake.
- It's not her in the grave.
- It's not her body.
- Of course it's her.
No. it's not! Her arm was broken!
- That arm's not broken!
- You're misremembering.
It was in a sling!
It was in a sling I remember that!
Yes. Yes. it was.
Because she had sprained her arm falling
from a tree trying to climb after you.
Trying to keep up after you.
No wonder you blocked it from your memory.
I understand how desperately
you want to believe she's alive.
I know about your…
your failed businesses.
And how your fortunes changed
when Mother was sent away. Explain that.
You know why my business went under?
Because I was here
looking after your mother.
She wasn't well. Sherlock.
Long before Beatrice died.
And after she went away. I buried myself
in work until my fortunes improved.
- There is nothing sinister about it.
- Only two people saw the body.
O-Only you and the groundskeeper.
That is simply untrue. The doctor…
He issued the death certificate.
He saw her.
- I can't believe we're even having this--
- A doctor who didn't even know
- what Beatrice looked like!
- Enough. I've been more than patient.
Why would you bring a doctor
all the way from Oxford?
That was your mother's idea!
She was an old friend of his!
He was an old friend of hers!
She wanted him to be here!
Listen to me.
Sherlock.
Listen. It was the worst day of our lives.
Of course you…
Of course you find it confusing.
Do you… Do you really think that I'm…
I'm… I'm… I'm…
I'm capable of something so heinous?
- Imagination can be a curse.
- I'm sorry.
You stay away from him!
That's a lie. About the doctor.
It's a lie!
How many others are there?
Cordelia. my love.
You don't remember.
James told me
what they found in that grave.
Yes. Beatrice!
Where is she?
We all just need to calm down.
Oh. do we?
Get him!
Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
♪ Hey son. I'm looking forwards ♪
♪ You're aiming backwards
Of this I'm sure ♪
♪ Have you had enough?
Are you feeling rough? ♪
♪ Does your skull hurt? ♪
♪ Well if it's war ♪
♪ I'm waiting ♪
♪ Right here now. I'm waiting ♪
♪ For someone or something ♪
♪ To take me. to take me over ♪
♪ Days ♪
♪ Days are forgotten ♪
♪ Now it's all over ♪
♪ You've simply forgotten ♪
♪ How to disappear ♪
Uh. that's. uh…
Most mysterious. Most mysterious.
Um. what is. sir?
What? What is what. young man?
What is most mysterious?
Well. no sign of skin discolouration.
no lingering smell
that would indicate poisoning.
no sign of a heart attack.
no blood vessels burst.
as you would expect.
and no flesh wounds. uh. of any sort.
So. the man has been murdered and
you're telling me that we don't know how?
What I'm telling you
is that the body is in excellent health.
Yes. apart from the rather
unfortunate fact that he is dead.
Hmm.
- What is this?
- That's the contents of his airways.
The sort of thing that you would
expect in a drowning victim.
Except he didn't drown.
I was there. It was on dry land.
Would you excuse us
for a moment. please. sir?
- Yes. certainly. young man.
-  Thank you so much.
Do you know what he was working on?
Because if you do. now is the time.
No. It was. um.
something for the government.
- Most secretive.
- So. he and Professor Malik.
they were working together. is that right?
Yes. Although. he never shared
any of the details with me.
You neither?
No. Ah.
Are we getting anywhere?
Not really. Lestrade. No.
Each question leads to more questions.
Like fighting the Hydra.
Lestrade?
What do you have for me?
A wire came for you. sir.
Oh.
I have been summoned.
- Who is she?
- We don't know.
They would've got a body
from the hospital or the poorhouse.
It's not hard to do.
Do you think she might still be alive?
- I don't know.
- But it is a possibility?
Yes.
It is a possibility.
Where are you going?
To find her.
And where is Professor Malik now?
I'm afraid I don't know. sir.
- And the Chinese assassin?
- Whereabouts also unknown. sir.
Mr Holmes.
your handling of this whole thing
has been nothing short of appalling.
Well. perhaps if you gentlemen
had been a little more forthcoming
with me from the start.
I might have been better placed
to protect Sir Bucephalus.
Are you insinuating this is our fault?
I can say it more plainly if you prefer.
- Holmes--
-  I believe that Hodge was killed
owing to a secret government project
based out of Oxford.
the details of which
you have refused to share with me.
But I suspect whatever he was working on
was highly dangerous.
Hodge died working for this government.
I need to know what you know.
How does a man show
signs of drowning on dry land?
Don't try to confuse us with riddles. sir.
You were sent to Oxford
to assist Sir Bucephalus
with the new science building.
Now he's dead.
On your watch.
You are done here. sir.
Your career with Her Majesty's government
is at an end.
- Sir. if I may--
- That will be all.
Good day.
Tell me everything
that you've uncovered so far.
Well. we think it was the groundskeeper
who actually took Beatrice.
- Not Nathan.
- Yes. Nathan.
Father paid off his debts
just after Beatrice disappeared.
My darling. he was always so kind.
Well. Father was with us
at the picnic the entire time.
So. he would've needed an accomplice.
And the groundskeeper
would've squirrelled her off the estate.
So. he would've needed to… Thank you…
take her as far away from here as possible
- without anyone noticing.
- Did he have a cart or a trap?
Yes. he had a cart for his deliveries.
Nathan did deliveries?
- Game.
- Yes.
Father used to hunt game on the estate.
Pheasants and rabbits.
And Beatrice would never eat the rabbits.
She used to give them all names.
So. there was lots left over
and Nathan would sell it
once a week from his cart.
So Nathan renders her unconscious
and hides her in the cart.
Underneath the sacks
of pheasants and rabbits.
And then it's a standard delivery
and he draws no attention to himself.
Do you remember where
he'd make these deliveries to?
No. darling. I-I have no idea.
The game book.
The estate game book.
Everything that was shot and sold
has been recorded in there.
Nathan Burford makes a delivery
the day after Beatrice supposedly dies.
Isn't that a peculiar day to go
about your business as usual?
A brace of pheasants.
Four rabbits.
And a hare.
Delivered to an address in Highgate.
That's the best part of
60 miles from here.
Where no one would know her.
I will get Crowle to saddle some horses.
and I promise to wire news
as soon as I have it.
Oh. no.
I'm coming with you.
If Beatrice is out there.
I'm going to find her.
With or without you.
Well. that's you told.
Oh. Get out from under my feet!
Go on. you little tykes.
Go play over there.
- Who are you then?
- Mycroft Holmes.
I was wondering
if your good husband might be home.
My good husband.
I only have the one.
- Visitor.
- Thank you. light of my life.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
A little early. isn't it. Constable?
To be on the cider.
I'm drowning my ambition. Mr Holmes.
Scotland Yard.
That's what I had my sights on.
But after everything that's gone down.
Hodge dead. Shou'an fled.
I'll be lucky to keep my job in Oxford.
Constable.
it is a safe bet. is it not.
to assume that Professor Malik
killed Sir Bucephalus Hodge?
- It is.
- Well. then.
is it also a safe bet to say
that if we were
to apprehend Professor Malik.
we could also rescue both of our careers?
- I'm listening.
- When we were at the police station
in Oxford. you mentioned
Professor Malik having a file.
- What of it?
- What was in it?
Nothing. Just his name and his address
in Oxford. which we've already searched.
But if he had no criminal record.
why bother to create a file
for him in the first place?
Answer.
There was something in that file before
that has since been taken--
- So. where's the arrest report?
- Worth another gander. don't you think?
I'll get my coat.
Thank you.
Hello.
Can I help you?
Uh. yes.
We're looking for a young girl.
W-We have reason to believe
that she was brought here
about 12 years ago.
Um. this is her.
I'm afraid I've never seen her.
Now I bid you good day.
I would ask you to stop pestering me.
Her name is Beatrice.
I-I'm her mother.
My name's Cordelia Holmes.
Until yesterday.
I believed that she was dead.
I now have reason to believe
that she may have been brought here.
Tell me anything you know.
Anything at all.
I-I'm asking you. I'm…
I'm begging you. Please help me.
We didn't know her name.
so we called her Hannah.
Because she came to us as a blessing.
Uh. I couldn't have children of my own.
you see. Mrs Holmes.
And we thought that she was an orphan.
And it was Nathan Burford
who brought her here?
He said he was from the orphanage.
There's been a terrible accident.
A fire at the house. so you're gonna
stay with Mrs Tilcott for a while.
Hello. little one.
We tried to give her a good life.
I am sure you did.
I gave her all the love I had.
"Gave."
You said. "Gave."
She's not here. is she?
She's gone?
Yes. She left us
when she was 14.
We woke up one morning
and she had written a note thanking us
and saying that she didn't
want us looking for her.
And you have no idea where she went?
- No.
-  Mrs Tilcott.
could I see her room?
What was she like?
Bright.
Determined.
Stubborn.
-  Anything?
-  Not yet.
Did she call you Mother?
- I'm so sorry.
- No. no. Please…
Please don't apologise.
I can see that this was
a happy and loving home.
She loved nature.
We'd get her those on her birthday.
A different one every year.
You would buy her these?
No need to lie to us now. Mrs Tilcott.
No. Mrs Tilcott. just anything you can
tell us that might help us to find her.
They were sent.
Where do they come from?
Sent from whom?
I never learnt his name. I never met him.
He was her benefactor.
That… That was all I knew.
And there was never any
return address on the parcels?
- None.
- Do forgive me.
Steel pin. Lacquered preventing rust
from the moisture inside the thorax.
Specialist equipment.
Only one place in London makes these.
Annual commission.
Beatrice was sent a butterfly
every year on her birthday.
- And paid for it by Silas?
- No name.
But they gave me an address.
Bedford Row. Holborn. Please. sir.
Darling?
Apologies.
Manners. Shirley.
Mm-hmm.
Constable Lestrade.
Mycroft Holmes.
Leave the door open.
Kishore Malik.
As I said. it's empty.
Someone trying to protect him. you think?
Look at this.
The ink was wet when the document
was put into the file.
Well. I can't read it.
It's… It's backwards.
Never leave home
without a dressing mirror. Constable.
Like so…
Two names. two addresses.
First is undoubtedly Malik's.
The second is harder to read.
Looks like "Alvie Gordon.
Shelbourne Hotel. Bayswater. London."
I don't suppose she'll know who I am.
She won't remember me after all this time.
And she's been raised
by another woman. so…
Now. now. Mrs Holmes.
You never forget your mother.
I certainly won't forget mine.
James. what happened to your mother?
Well. she's long passed.
She had the consumption.
I was only a little lad at the time.
You poor thing. I'm so sorry.
But there's not a day that goes by
that I don't think of her.
And I promise you
it will be the same for your Beatrice.
-  You are such a kind man.
- Well. you bring out the best in me.
And you have such a beautiful smile.
Driver!
Will you kindly stop it?
I wasn't referring to
the whistling. James.
- Kindly stop what?
- Flirting with my mother.
- I'm doing no such thing.
- I know you. You can't help yourself.
What I cannot help. Sherlock.
is if people find my charm irresistible.
You can't deny your mother's
a very beautiful woman.
And I certainly wouldn't kick her
out of bed for eating biscuits.
I am serious. James.
Cease. And desist.
Please.
This is the address for
Alvie Gordon. Esquire.
If your cute little
mirror trick is correct.
Good afternoon.
We're looking for an Alvie Gordon.
- Yes. of course.
- I'm Mr Gordon.
Perfect.
We're looking for Professor Malik.
Kishore Malik.
I'm sorry.
I don't know anyone by that name.
Strange that. sir.
Seeing as this address
was listed on his arrest report.
Perhaps this is best discussed
in my office.
Thank you.
Now.
What's all this about?
I couldn't possibly trouble you
for a glass of water. could I?
Wait here.
Thank you so much.
A receipt from Hatchards. the bookshop.
for a Moody's Guide. latest edition.
Might I ask what you think you're doing?
As I said. sir.
we're trying to find Professor Malik.
And as I said. I don't know him.
Have you recently purchased
a travel guide. sir?
I thought I might take a holiday.
This receipt mentions that
you paid to have it gift-wrapped.
Travelling with someone. are we?
What exactly is your relationship
with the professor?
We have the arrest report. Mr Gordon.
Someone tried to suppress it.
but recently it came into our possession.
Now. as far as I'm concerned.
how a man chooses
to live his life is his own affair.
But many in my profession
may hold a different view entirely.
Fortunately. for you. I'm able to ensure
the arrest report remains hidden.
As I'm sure you would prefer.
Yes.
Very much so.
So. tell me.
where is Professor Malik?
Paris.
Well. well. well.
Constable Lestrade.
Bluff and blackmail
all in the same breath.
You'll go far at Scotland Yard.
I'm quite sure.
I won't be able to come with you to Paris.
Oh. that is a shame.
I have to get back to work. Can't leave
Mrs Lestrade with her hands full.
Not to mention the goats.
Find Malik.
Yes. If I do…
- When you do.
- …I'll be sure to let your superiors know
quite how invaluable you were.
- Thank you. Mr Holmes.
- Please. call me Mycroft.
Primroses. two bundles a penny.
Sweet violets. penny a bunch.
Has he come out?
Not yet.
He's the only one
that can lead us to Malik.
-  Sweet violets.
- Bread Street.
-  Where's he going?
-  Bread Street. Cheapside.
Cheapside. please.
Can you stand?
Let me see.
Hang in there.
I'm going to get someone.
No time. You must follow him.
Esad is our only route to Professor Malik.
It's too late. Esad is long gone.
No.
I know where he's going.
I slipped this from his pocket.
Paris.
Girl…
- This is where he's going to be?
- Mm-hmm.
Girl…
You are amazing.
You must go.
I'm not leaving you.
You must stop Professor Malik.
You stop the creeping death.
For the memory of your parents.
You must promise.
All right.
I promise.
Hurry.
So. this is the address that
paid for Beatrice's butterflies?
It is.
And appears to be closed.
Oh.
Now. usually James and I would. of course.
wait until they are open
and come back in the morning.
Which is right and proper.
And what if we're not
being right and proper?
Do you have a hair pin. Mother?
Careful now.
This will make you our accomplice.
Oh. good.
Thank you.
Where did you learn how to do this?
Headmaster's office.
Used to break in. alter my school reports
before they were sent home.
Well. that didn't stop you
getting expelled from school. did it?
It stopped me getting expelled
from more schools than I would have.
Do you know. I'm realising
I have absolutely no idea who you are.
I am my mother's son.
- Care to do the honours?
- Go on. Live life on the edge.
We'll make a thief out of you yet.
Mrs Holmes.
What is this place?
Let's light her up and find out.
Good man.
Some sort of textile company.
Sherlock. look. This is Beatrice.
I mean. she's older. but…
About 14? That's definitely her.
I knew it.
I could feel that she is still alive.
Father's name.
That's definitely his signature.
A letter
from a customer in Vienna
regarding the purchase of muslin shirts.
So this is his office?
Importing textiles?
I don't understand.
Why would he hide that from us?
- We should hurry. James?
-  Yes. yes.
Silas's travel itinerary.
He's a busy man.
Brussels. Bordeaux. London to Monaco.
Amsterdam to Madrid.
There's a name here.
- Thérèse.
- Perhaps a female travel companion.
Well. whoever Thérèse is.
he's with her this weekend.
So. where is Thérèse?
All of those journeys were made by train.
- What are you doing?
-  Linear interpolation.
Brussels to Bordeaux.
- London…
- Monaco.
- …to Monaco. Amsterdam…
-  Madrid.
All of those journeys
intersect the same place.
Paris.
Oh. I saw something.
Look.
A guidebook to Paris.
Right. Well. Thérèse is not a woman.
Thérèse is the name of
a hotel in Paris in Rue Sainte-Anne.
Gosh. aren't I clever?
Right. Time to skedaddle.
Well done. Mother. When you're ready.
- Mrs Holmes.
- Yes. no. After you. This way.
Not that way.
-  This floor.
-  Yes. sir. Come on.
Good catch. sir.
Oh. goodness.
- Doesn't that hurt?
- Well. I never think to stop and ask them.
They're not policemen.
Police don't wear brown boots.
-  Well. who are they then?
- Well. we could ask them.
- Or we could run.
-  Come on!
- Oi. come on now!
- Stop!
- Run!
- Don't move! Stop!
- Oh. yes! Oh. yes! I'm running!
- Yes. yes.
Sherlock! Where are we going?
I'm not sure! Yet!
What are we doing?
Thinking.
Step aside. Mother.
Giddy up. hyah. giddy up.
Hup. hup. hup. Hyah!
This world of yours. Sherlock.
It is rather fun. isn't it?
Yes. I suppose it is.
- Right.
- Well…
To Paris?
Now.
they are in the midst of a revolution.
What? Again?
How many revolutions
does a country need?
Some parts of the city
remain relatively unscathed.
but we will have to navigate one
or two barricades
to get to where we need to go.
Oh. you are too focused
on the obstacles. my friend.
That's as far as I go.
How do we get to Hotel Thérèse?
You'll have to get past the barricades.
Good luck.
- Merci.
-  Merci.
This way! This way! Get down!
Through here.
We are friends! Friends!
-  English?
- Yes. yes. We're English.
We do not like the English.
Uh. how do you feel about the Irish?
We like the Irish.
What luck. I'm Irish.
Long live the revolution!
So. what do you propose?
I don't shoot you. but I do shoot them?
No. w-we'd quite like if you didn't shoot
any of us if it's all the same to you?
Um. w-we're just looking for my husband.
He's on your side.
H-He would lay down his life
for the revolution.
Then get over here.
Merci.
Madame.
James?
-  Here she is. Hotel Thérèse.
-  All right.
- Let's find a spot and watch the place.
- Wait for him to show.
There's no time to wait.
We have to find Bea.
Ah.
Good evening. sir.
Madame.
I have come to join my husband.
Mr Silas Holmes.
Madame. Mr Holmes is not here at present.
Perhaps you'd be good enough to tell me.
where I might find him?
A man must be allowed to have
his own private business. Madame.
Monsieur.
I am tired.
I am hungry.
And I have recently
escaped from an asylum.
You really don't want me
causing a scene in your nice hotel.
She's quite lethal with a shotgun.
We're looking for Silas Holmes.
Left here about 15 minutes ago.
- Where was he going?
- No idea.
He didn't take a carriage.
So then he went somewhere close?
Which way?
- The direction?
- Boulevard de Sebastopol.
North.
- What was he wearing?
- Wearing?
Top hat.
- Cloak.
- The Opera?
Wrong direction.
So what's within walking distance.
where a man would go.
dressed up for a night on the tiles?
Whisper it.
Les Folies Bergère.
Darling. I'm only sorry
you have to be here with your mother.
Quite all right.
Oh!
I finally found where I belong.
Outside the world burns.
inside they dance.
Never underestimate
the human need for diversion.
Just keep them entertained.
you'll have them in the palm of your hand.
The face of an angel! I am in paradise.
The things you could teach me.
Whatever you want. for a fee.
A fee he can't afford.
Now if you wouldn't mind.
I'd quite like to find Silas.
Mycroft.
- Silas.
- No.
Mycroft.
Mother.
What is Mycroft doing here?
- Sherlock?
-  My dear brother.
You brought Mother to Paris?
Have you finally
lost your marbles. brother dear?
It wasn't his decision. darling.
I'm fed up of people
making decisions on my behalf.
Well. I must say. it does seem
to be rather agreeing with you.
Yes. I-I do find this life
of adventure rather suits me.
I just wish
I'd discovered it before. darling.
Um. sorry.
I'm just not used to--
Seeing me like this? I know.
Neither am I.
I'm finding it so liberating.
- Finished?
- Yes.
- What are you doing here?
- Ah.
Following him.
Malik?
More to the point.
what are you all doing here?
We've been following him.
Father.
What's he doing here?
It appears those two gulls
know each other.
Curiouser and curiouser.
Would anybody care to enlighten me
as to what the hell is going on?
We think Beatrice might still be alive.
- I'm sorry. What did you say?
- We think Beatrice might still be alive.
Yes. I heard you. Sherlock.
But what did you just say?
Darling. I know that Bea is alive.
and Silas knows where she is.
Darling. He's on the move.
- No time to explain.
- Sherlock.
There's a guard.
- Mycroft.
- Yes? What?
- Oh.
-  Madame.
Madame. are you okay?
I'm feeling dizzy.
- Monsieur…
-  Let me help you.
Thank you.
Well. no one just vanishes.
This one looks rather young.
Gentlemen. I appreciate
you all being here this evening.
I know you all have busy lives.
but I think you'll find
this will be worth your while.
Moment of silence.
Moment of silence. please.
Please. gentlemen.
settle down. settle down.
Thank you. I trust you enjoyed
the festivities upstairs.
to which we shall return.
but for now. we must get down to business.
Gentlemen. I know you stand here today
with the same question on your minds.
How do you take back control of your city?
How do you take back control
of your country?
Impossible. some might say.
As a famous man once said.
"'Impossible' is a word only found
in the dictionary of fools."
What I am offering you
here today. gentlemen.
what Professor Malik here has developed…
will change the face of modern warfare.
Odourless. colourless. silent.
deadly.
This nerve agent is unlike anything
the modern world has seen before.
Killing butterflies is
hardly our mission. sir.
Indeed. General. Quite so.
Bring out the deplorable.
You see. what I have here.
in the right concentrations.
will work on a barricade. a neighbourhood.
or even an entire city.
You no longer need armies
to defeat your enemies. General.
You simply need me.
Or. more precisely.
you need what I'm selling.
For those of you
who wish to place an order.
it's only fitting that we should meet
at the famous two corners.
where you can contact Mr Esad Kasgarli.
No. no!
Et voilà.
Father!
Sherlock?
Don't!
♪ Remember me when you're the one
Who's silver screened ♪
You always dreamed ♪
♪ Remember me
Whenever noses start to bleed ♪
♪ Remember me ♪
♪ Special needs ♪
♪ And just 19. a sucker's dream ♪
♪ I guess I thought you had the flavour ♪
♪ Just 19. a dream obscene ♪
♪ With six months off for bad behaviour ♪
♪ Remember me
When you clinch your movie deal ♪
♪ And think of me stuck in my chair
That has four wheels ♪
♪ Remember me
Through flash photography and screams ♪
♪ Remember me ♪
♪ Special dreams ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm